(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-03T22:57:54.425936",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
「もうどうなってもいいや」
[Song: Mou Dou Natte Mo Iiya]
泥まみれのファンタジー
A mud-splattered fantasy,
空字なぞるなぞなぞ
riddles tracing words drawn in the air.
本能のままに孤独等に惹かれる衝動
An impulse drawn to solitude, following pure instinct.
もうどうなってもいいや
I don't care what happens anymore.
あなたのことが知りたいだけ
I just want to know about you.
星に願う本当の気持ち
My true feeling of wishing upon a star.
苦しみ紛れの言い訳は
Excuses born out of desperation...
いらない 意味ない 君はどう？
...are unneeded, meaningless. How about you?
一番を失ったみたいだ
It feels like I've lost what mattered most,
呪いのあとの類で
as a sort of after-effect of a curse.
同じことばかり繰り返して
Repeating the exact same things over and over,
誰かの歩幅で踊ってる
dancing at someone else's pace.
誰かが取り繕う誰かになんて
Becoming someone whom someone else patched together...
なれやしないよ 魔法みたいな恋の主人公なら
...I could never be that. If I'm the protagonist of a magical romance,
最後はどうなってもハッピーエンディングにしてよ
make it a happy ending no matter how it turns out in the end.
もうどうなってもいいや
I don't care what happens anymore,
逆さまに落ちていった 重力のない逃避行
falling upside down in an escape without gravity.
秘密の夜が交わってどこへ行こう
Secret nights intertwine, where shall we go?
一切合切持って行って 残すことなく人生を賭け
Take everything away, betting our lives without leaving anything behind,
目合える星に思いを馳せて
letting your thoughts drift to the star where our eyes can meet.
好きが溢れてるなんて この世は全て終わった愛の歌
Saying love is overflowing... this world is full of ended love songs.
もうどうなってもいいや
I don't care what happens anymore.
曖昧な線に濡れてる
Swaying along ambiguous lines,
君の瞳の奥へピント合わせてぼかす
I focus deep into your eyes, then blur them.
誰も触れたことのない 真実の冷雨に濡れた体
My body soaked in the true cold rain that no one has ever touched,
ざわめく ギラつく 簡単じゃないから
stirring, glaring, because it's not simple,
もっともっともっともっと
more, more, more, more...
遠くに暗く広がった
Spreading darkly into the distance,
さらけ出すように満ちてくるライフ
a life brimming over as if exposing everything,
魔法みたいな恋のものなんてそんなもんだって
saying that's all a magical romance is.
傷つきたいわけじゃないけど バッドエンドの抜け出しの勇気を
It's not that I want to get hurt, but give me the courage to escape a bad ending,
もうどうなってもいいや
I don't care what happens anymore.
火花みたいに燃えたいから
Because I want to burn like sparks,
いつかの日は忘れてしまって
forgetting about someday in the future.
解んないね なんて感情の
"I don't understand", what kind of emotion...
絞り挟んで 特別になるコントロール
...compressing it into a control that becomes special...
惑わされて 静寂と...
...being bewildered, along with silence...
誰と逃避行を
With whom shall I run away...
ぬくもり感じれる距離まで引き寄せて
Pull me close enough to feel your warmth.
月の涙が降ったこの夜はまるで
On this night where moon's tears fell, it's like...
Stranger, I WAS A CAT
まさか罠に落ちていった 宛てのない逃避行を
To think I fell into a trap, an aimless getaway,
秘密の夜が交わって虜
intertwined with secret nights, leaving me captive.
一切合切持っていって もう少しだけ人生を歌う
Take it all away, as I sing of life just a little longer.
混じり合う星に思い馳せて
Thinking of the blending stars,
月が綺麗だなんて言葉は
words like "the moon is beautiful"
すべてワンダー I want now
are all wonder, I want now.
夜のぬくもりのファンタジー 空想の夢の姿 色々な街に踊るように高まる衝動
Fantasy of nighttime warmth, figures of imaginary dreams, an impulse swelling as if dancing in various towns...
もうどうなってもいいや
I don't care what happens anymore.
ビビデバ
Bibbidi-ba
つまらないデイズ もう散々ね
Boring days, I've really had enough!
奇跡願っているだけの人生
A life spent just wishing for miracles...
Watch me do 呪術秘中
Watch me do, secret sorcery,
トリック無しのマジック
magic with no tricks.
I wanna be free! だってまだふりだし
I wanna be free! Cause I'm still at square one.
Hey タクシー ちょっと宇宙まで
Hey taxi, take me to space!
秒針は音を立てて 夜を急かす魔物のように
The second hand ticks loudly like a monster rushing the night.
人生は一瞬にして溶ける魔法
Life is magic that melts in an instant,
それならば駆け抜け 翻して想い通り
so run through it, turn things around, just as you wish!
それならば駆け抜けて STORY
So run right through it, STORY!
おしゃまな馬車 飛び乗って Driving
Hopping onto a stylish carriage, driving,
あたしは大変身メイクアップ！
I'm making a big makeover!
我儘のまにまに 燦めきに注意
Following my own whims, beware of the dazzle,
洒落た街で Dancing
dancing in a stylish town.
さようなら グッドバイ劣等感
Farewell, goodbye inferiority complex!
何時かは 喝采 クラップ オーディエンス
Someday, applause, clap, audience,
皆々 御唱和あれ！
everyone, sing along!
BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOOWA Yeah!
混がっても仕方が無いから 終電のナイ
There's no point getting mixed up, so there's no last train...
BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOOWA Yeah!
今夜に明日など無いならば 自由に乗ったもん勝ちでしょう
If there's no tomorrow tonight, then whoever dances freely wins, right?
Dance! どんな問題も解は一つ
Dance! No matter the problem, there's only one answer.
白紙も正解も間違いも愛す 本当のあたしの理想
Loving blank sheets, correct answers, and mistakes: the true ideal me.
なんだか世界は限界の気配がして
Somehow the world feels like it's at its limit,
ただただ安心じゃあ心配 今すぐ Jumpin' Jumpin' out
mere safety makes me worried; jumpin', jumpin' out right now!
チッチキボンバー チッチキボンバー 異様に抱く違和感 抱く日々に
Chicchiki bomba, chicchiki bomba, in these days filled with strange discomfort,
ギリギリ爆発気味 たった今発散してしまおうか
on the verge of exploding, shall I unleash it all right now?
まだまだビビるな 巧みに乱射
Don't flinch yet, skillfully fire away!
一発じゃ撃ち足りないわ
One shot isn't enough!
遂に導き出した君にアンサー
The answer I finally derived for you:
灰になるまで踊っていよう
let's keep dancing until we turn to ash!
BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOOWA Yeah!
おしゃまな馬車 飛び乗って Driving
Hopping onto a stylish carriage, driving,
あたしは大変身メイクアップ！
I'm making a big makeover!
我儘のまにまに 燦めきに注意
Following my own whims, beware of the dazzle,
洒落た街で Dancing
dancing in a stylish town.
さようなら グッドバイ劣等感
Farewell, goodbye inferiority complex!
何時かは 喝采 クラップ オーディエンス
Someday, applause, clap, audience,
皆々 御唱和あれ！
everyone, sing along!
BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOOWA Yeah!
混がっても仕方が無いから 終電のナイ
There's no point getting mixed up, so there's no last train...
BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOOWA Yeah!
今夜に明日など無いならば 自由に乗ったもん勝ちでしょう
If there's no tomorrow tonight, then whoever dances freely wins, right?
ありがとうございました！
Thank you so much!
ということで2曲お届けさせていただきました
And so, I've performed two songs for you.
皆さん楽しんでますかー？
Is everyone enjoying themselves?
今回は全編アコースティック編成ということで
This time, as it's an all-acoustic arrangement,
今までの生誕ライブにはない
unlike previous birthday live performances,
しっとりとしたテイストでお送りしていこうと思いますよ
I hope to bring you a mellow and relaxed atmosphere.
8周年の感謝の気持ちを込めて
Filled with gratitude for these 8 years,
じっくりと音楽に浸ってもらえると嬉しいです
I hope you can thoroughly immerse yourselves in the music.
それでは次の曲聴いてください
Now then, please listen to the next song.
月に向かって撃て
"Shoot for the Moon"
Woo...
うかがっている明かり
A light I've been watching,
手を伸ばして思い出す
Reaching out, I remember.
浮かれたくはないわね
I don't want to get carried away.
聞かせたい声
The voice I want you to hear...
不可能の可能性だ
It's the possibility within the impossible.
君が誰なんだか知っていた
I knew who you were.
証明しよう 僕ら本当はどうしたい？
Let me prove it—what do we really want to do?
逃げたいと耳塞いだ瞬間 心臓を叩いてた スナイパー
The moment I covered my ears to run, a sniper pounded in my heart.
スナイパー 変わらない表情に
Sniper... with an unchanging expression,
銃口を突き立てて
Point the barrel straight at it.
情熱は月に向かって撃て スナイパー
Shoot your passion toward the moon, sniper!
未来はどうやら気にしたい
It seems I do want to care about the future.
喉が渇いたって後悔はないわ
Even if my throat grows parched, I have no regrets.
擦り剥いて埋めるの 99%
Scraped up, filling in 99% of it.
小指には衝動
Impulse on my pinky finger.
本当はどうしたいんだっけ？
What was it I really wanted to do again?
合図して ハートショットに乗せて
Give the signal, carry it on a heart shot.
あっという間に
In the blink of an eye,
一番乗りでフライングしても
Even if I jump the gun and take first place,
あっという間に
In the blink of an eye.
擦れ違った風も
Even the wind we brushed past,
ぶつけ合った悔しさも
And the frustration we clashed with,
向き合うように照らす
Light us up as if to make us face it.
銃口は絶対になれ
Make the muzzle absolute.
もしも人生が10分なら 7分はあなたと賭けに
If life were only 10 minutes, 7 would be spent betting with you.
ネオンのようなアトラクションで タッチダウン
Touchdown at a neon-like attraction!
臆病を好きに燃やしていけ
Burn through your cowardice as you please,
スター まだ見ぬゴールは気にしたい
Star! I want to care about the unseen goal.
夢も照らす圧倒的軌道上
On an overwhelming orbit illuminating even dreams.
吸い込んで一息ついて 99% アナタを咲かせ
Take a deep breath, 99%, let yourself bloom.
本当はどうしたいんだっけ？
What was it I really wanted to do again?
追いつくわ ハートショットに向けて
I'll catch up, aimed straight for a heart shot.
証明書 届かなくたって
Even if the certificate never arrives...
情熱は月に向かって撃て スナイパー
Shoot your passion toward the moon, sniper!
未来は今日も僕ら次第
The future is up to us again today.
誰が笑ったって後悔はないわ
No matter who laughs, I have no regrets.
擦り抜けて埋めるの 99%
Slipping through to fill in 99%.
小指には衝動
Impulse on my pinky finger.
本当はどうしたいんだっけ？
What was it I really wanted to do again?
合図して ハートショットに乗せて
Give the signal, carry it on a heart shot.
あっという間に
In the blink of an eye,
一番乗りでフライングしても
Even if I jump the gun and take first place,
あっという間に
In the blink of an eye.
飛び込んでいけ フライングしても
Dive right in, even if you jump the gun.
あっという間に
In the blink of an eye.
あなただけに フライングしても
Just for you, even if I jump the gun...
綺麗事を吐くその口が
That mouth spitting sugarcoated words...
君の事を苦しめるから
...because it torments you so.
同じ言葉ばかりの日常に
In a daily life filled with the same empty words,
ああ 意味を求めて寄り添い合うの
Ah, seeking meaning as we huddle together.
ひしめき合うカラーフィルターの奥で笑ってる
Smiling behind the crowded color filters,
散々憎んだ狡猾さが
The cunningness I hated so much...
今 自分なりの生き方なのに
Though it's my own way of living now,
潔癖な思考に縛られたままで
Bound by fastidious thoughts,
強がるくせに
Trying to act tough,
唇を噛む
...yet biting my lip.
分かってない素振りをしてばかり
Feigning ignorance,
ああ そんぶりをしてばかり
Ah, doing nothing but pretending...
綺麗事を吐くその口が
That mouth spitting sugarcoated words,
嫌いだから歌を歌うんだ
I hate it, and that's why I sing.
諦めているその顔が
That resigned look on your face,
僕の事を曇らせる
Clouds my heart.
こんな声だって伝わらなくて
Even a voice like this fails to reach,
もっと完璧な言葉を紡ぎたくて
Wishing to weave ever more perfect words,
ずっと欲張って
Always being greedy,
きっと間違えて
Surely making mistakes,
今日も転げ落ちる
Tumbling down once again...
不完全な朝
In an incomplete morning,
本音も言えない日常には
In a daily life where I can't even speak my true feelings,
ただ「理想なんて」と嘲笑う声
there are only voices ridiculing, "What ideals?"
言い返す言葉も選べずに
Unable to even choose words to talk back,
ただ増していく痛み
the pain just keeps growing.
虚勢を張る衝動で隠して
Hiding behind an impulse of bravado,
綺麗なままで生きてたいのか
do you want to live remaining pure?
諦めを塗り重ねて
Piling up give-ups,
「本当」が見えなくなってしまうんだ
I end up losing sight of what's real.
綺麗事
[Title: Pure Talk]
綺麗事を吐くその口が
Because I hate that mouth...
...that mouth spitting pretty talk...
綺麗事を吐くその口が
嫌いだから歌を歌うんだ
...I sing songs.
諦めているその顔が
That face of giving up...
君のことを苦しめる
...it is what causes you pain.
こんな声だって
Even if it's a voice like this,
伝わらなくたって
even if it doesn't reach,
もっと完璧な言葉を紡ぎたくて
I want to weave more perfect words.
ずっと欲張って
Always being greedy,
きっと間違えて
surely making mistakes,
それでも歌おう
even so, let me sing,
不完全だから
because I am incomplete.
ありがとうございました
Thank you very much.
楽しんでますか？
Are you enjoying yourselves?
さあ、みんなね
Now then, everyone,
武道館再演で出したあの重大発表のティザー
the teaser for that major announcement we showed at the Budokan rerun,
あの内容が気になっている頃なのではないでしょうか？
aren't you curious about what it's all about right now?
それからみんな、もちろん見つけてくれましたよね？
And also, of course you all found it, right?
先週の月曜日からある場所で屋外広告もね、出ていたりして
Since last Monday, outdoor ads have been put up in a certain place,
きっと今頃ね、「何が起きるんだ！」って
and I bet by now you're wondering, "What's gonna happen?!"
ただならぬ空気を感じてドギマギしているんじゃないかなと思うんですけれど
feeling this extraordinary atmosphere and getting all flustered,
まずはね、言葉じゃなくて
first of all, rather than words,
今日の告知に向けて音楽に込めてみんなに伝えたいなと思い、こういった編成で今回やらせてもらっております
I wanted to convey my feelings through music for today's announcement, so we're performing with this acoustic setup today.
アコースティックってさ、なんかエモくて
Acoustic performances have this emotional feel,
今までのことをこう、思い返すような
making you look back on everything up until now,
なんかノスタルジーな気持ちになったりしますよね？
giving you a nostalgic feeling, doesn't it?
いつもはテンションを上げてくれるようなあの曲が
That song that usually gets your energy pumped up,
今日はね、また違った形でみんなに響いたらいいなと思って歌わせていただいております
today I'm singing it in a different way, hoping it resonates with you differently.
楽曲のアレンジもそうだし、この生誕配信自体もそうだし
Not only the song arrangement, but this birthday stream itself as well,
新しい一面を見せながらも
while showing a new side of myself,
何よりこの8年間、みんなでね、一緒にやってきた、紡いできた
above all, over these past eight years that we've spent together,
絆みたいなものがしっかり感じられるライブにできたら嬉しいです
I'd be happy if this live performance lets you clearly feel the bond we've woven.
それでは次の曲に行きましょう
Well then, let me move on to the next song.
ムーンライト
Moonlight.
遠くまで歩こうよ 裸足で
Let's walk far away, barefoot,
小さな幸せを見つけて
finding small moments of happiness.
湿った月が窓を覗いて
The damp moon peeked through the window
「こっちへおいで」と笑った
and smiled, "Come over here."
似た者同士なんだよな 案外
We're two of a kind after all, unexpectedly.
分から合い合えない部分も安牌
Even the parts we can't understand are safe.
月明かりをめくった残像
An afterimage turning over the moonlight,
誰かにとっての普通をしよう
let's do what's normal for someone else.
私と踊ってよ ムーンライト
Dance with me, Moonlight.
ねぇ こっちで遊ぼう サニーサイド
Hey, let's play over here, Sunnyside.
隠し事ばっかのインサイド
An inside full of secrets,
ねぇ こっちで遊ぼうよ ミッドナイト
hey, let's play over here, Midnight.
この重たいカーテンを開けて
Open these heavy curtains,
嘘みたいな夜を抜け出そう
and let's escape this night like a lie.
まだやることばっかで忙しいけど
I'm still busy with so much to do, but...
あの1等星になって街をハイジャックしようぜ
Let's become that first-magnitude star and hijack the town.
このメロウな今日をずっと泳いでいこう
Let's keep swimming through this mellow day forever.
泳いでいこう
Let me keep swimming on.
街明かりを奪って
Stealing the city lights,
月で待ち合わせ
let's meet on the moon.
届きそうで届かない
So close, yet out of reach,
あなたはムーンライト
you are moonlight.
理由もなく寂しい夜が来て
A lonely night arrives for no reason at all,
古くなっていく空気の上で眠りたい
and I want to sleep atop the stale air.
似た者同士なんだから 厄介
We're so alike, which makes it troublesome.
隠し事すら抱えて 厄介
Carrying secrets between us is troublesome, too.
まだやることばっかで忙しいけど
I'm still busy with so much to do,
おやすみ
but good night.
あの光の方へ どこか遠い方へ
Toward that light, somewhere far away.
このメロウな今日をずっと泳いでいこう
Let's keep swimming through this mellow day forever.
尽きない悩みの種 話を聞かせて
Tell me about your endless worries.
私とあなただけの世界で
In a world belonging only to you and me,
あの1等星になって 街をハイジャックしようぜ
let's become a first-magnitude star and hijack the town.
このメロウな今日をずっと泳いでいこう
Let's keep swimming through this mellow day forever.
穴だらけの心で
With a heart full of holes,
あなただけを想って
thinking only of you,
眠れそうで眠れない こんな夜は
on a night like this where I can't fall asleep,
私と踊ってよ ムーンライト
dance with me, Moonlight.
せっかく仕事ばっかの人生
Since life is full of work anyway,
ねぇ こっちで遊ぼうよ
hey, come play over here.
街明かりを奪って
Stealing the city lights,
月で待ち合わせ
let's meet on the moon.
届きそうで届かない
So close, yet out of reach,
あなたはムーンライト
you are moonlight.
遠くまで歩こうよ 裸足で
Let's walk far away barefoot,
小さな幸せを見つけて
finding little moments of happiness.
湿った月が窓を覗いて
The damp moon peeks through the window
こっちへおいでと笑った
and smiles, saying "Come over here."
似た者同士なんだよね 案外
We're unexpectedly similar, aren't we?
分かり合えない部分も安牌
Even the parts we can't understand are safe bets.
月明かりをめくった残像
Afterimages left by peeling back the moonlight,
私にとっての普通でいよう
let's stay as what's normal to me.
実は、ここからスペシャルゲストに来てもらっています！
Actually, we have a special guest joining us from here on!
さあ、誰かわかるかな？
Now, I wonder if you can guess who it is?
それでは呼びましょう！
Well then, let's call him out!
イノタクさ〜ん！
Inotaku-san!
お久しぶりです。
It's been a while.
改めてよろしくお願いします。
Thanks again for having me.
来てくれて嬉しいです。ありがとうございます！
I'm so happy you're here. Thank you so much!
ここからはイノタクさんにも入ってもらって、
From here on, with Inotaku-san joining us as well,
さらなる特別編成で何曲か続けてお届けしていきますよ！
we'll be performing a few songs back-to-back in an even more special lineup!
イノタクさん、準備はいいですか？
Inotaku-san, are you ready?
よろしくお願いします。
Looking forward to it.
それでは聴いてください。
Please listen to this.
『夜を待つよ』
"Waiting for the Night."
夜を待つよ 夜を待つよ
I'm waiting for the night, waiting for the night.
夜を待つよ 待つのよ
I'm waiting for the night, I'm waiting.
今日もまたばっちりしっかり決まって
Looking sharp and totally ready again today,
君ははっきりきっぱり歌ってる
you're singing out clearly and decisively.
明けない夜は
"There's no such thing...
そんなものはないよと
...as a night that never ends,"
椰子の木がゆっくりゆっくりそよぐ
as the palm trees gently, gently sway.
僕はやっぱりさっぱり分かんない
Honestly, I don't get it at all.
ただひたすらに
I just blindly...
夜を待つよ
...wait for the night.
このままじゃだんだんだめになりそう
At this rate, I'm slowly gonna go to ruin.
夜を待つよ 夜を待つよ
I'm waiting for the night, waiting for the night.
きっとさんざんな目にあいそう
I'll probably go through terrible times.
夜を待つよ 待つのよ
I'm waiting for the night, I'm waiting.
耐え抜いてざんざん雨に降られて
Enduring it all while being soaked in heavy rain,
夜を待つよ 君を待つよ 待つのよ
I wait for the night, I wait for you, I'm waiting.
今は待つのよ
For now, I'm waiting.
濡れたまんま切っ先を研ぐのよ
While still wet, I sharpen my blade.
行き当たりばったりにっこり笑って
Smiling happily on a whim,
今日もごっこでホッとしたふりして
playing pretend today too, acting like I'm relieved.
あかさたなさえはまらないロンリネス
A loneliness that doesn't even fit into the basics,
もののけはあっちで
with specters over there...
あっちでこっちで踊って
Dancing here and there,
君はハッタリばかりかまして
you're talking big and showing off,
ぼくは
and I...
夜を待つよ
I wait for the night.
このままじゃどんどんダメになりそう
If things stay like this, I'll fall apart,
夜を待つよ 夜を待つよ
so I wait for the night, I wait for the night.
もっと混沌の海が理想
An ocean of chaos would be ideal,
夜を待つよ 待つのよ
I wait for the night, I wait for it.
美しい本当よりもひしゃげた
Rather than a beautiful truth,
夜を待つよ
I wait for a crushed night.
君を待つよ 待つのよ
I wait for you, I wait.
今は待つのよ
For now, I wait.
いつかきっときっかけは来るのよ
Someday, an opportunity will surely come.
唇でゆっくりゆっくり騙して
Deceiving slowly, slowly with my lips,
ぼくはポップでチープなふりして
I pretend to be pop and cheap.
真夜中までの夕暮れを泳いでは
Swimming through the dusk until midnight,
もののけはうっとりうっそり笑って
the specters smile enchantingly and falsely.
導火線が燃える中で今
While the fuse is burning right now,
嘘をつくの 夜が来るまでは
I tell lies, until the night comes.
夜が明ける千年まえからぼくら
Since a thousand years before dawn,
夜を待つよ 夜を待つよ
we wait for the night, we wait for the night.
君がぜんぜんわからないから
Because I don't understand you at all,
夜を待つよ 待つのよ
I wait for the night, I wait for it.
無理筋なペンチャン待ちでもいいの
Even an unlikely long shot will do,
夜を待つよ 夜を待つよ
I wait for the night, I wait for the night.
待つのよ
I wait.
君を待つのよ
I wait for you.
そうよもっと切っ先を研ぐのよ
That's right, sharpen the blade even more.
最後最後絶対笑うのよ
In the end, in the very end, I will definitely laugh.
君を待つのよ
I wait for you.
最後最後笑うのはぼくらだ
In the end, in the very end, we are the ones who will laugh.
だって僕は星だから
Because I'm a star,
Stellar Stellar
きっと君はもう気づいていた
I'm sure you already noticed
僕の心の奥で描いた
what I envisioned deep in my heart.
それがこれから話す陳腐な
It's just a cliché
モノローグさ
monologue I'm about to tell.
ずっと言えない言葉があった
There were words I could never say,
壊せない壁があったんだ ずっとさ
there were walls I couldn't break down, all along.
ふっと香り立つ朝の匂いが
The scent of morning wafting in the air
どうしようもなく憎らしくて
was so utterly hateful to me,
部屋の隅で膝を抱えて
I curled up in a corner of my room,
震えていた
trembling.
太陽なんていらないから
I don't need the sun,
明けないでいて
so please don't let dawn break.
その手を伸ばして誰かに届くように
Reach out that hand so it can touch someone.
僕だって君と同じ
Because I'm just like you,
特別なんかじゃないから
I'm nothing special after all.
そうさ僕は夜を歌うよ Stellar Stellar
That's right, I sing the night, Stellar Stellar,
ありったけの輝きで
with all the brilliance I possess.
今宵音楽はずっとずっと止まらない
Tonight, the music will never, ever stop.
そうさ僕がずっと成りたかったのは
Yes, what I always wanted to be
待ってるシンデレラじゃないさ
isn't a Cinderella who just waits,
迎えに行く王子様だ
it's the prince who goes to rescue her.
だって僕は星だから
Because I'm a star.
なんてありふれた話なんだ
What a commonplace story,
理想だけ書き連ねていた
just listing my ideals,
ノートの隅に眠るほんのワンシーンだ
just a single scene sleeping in the corner of a notebook.
あの星も泣いてるんだ
That star is crying too.
明けないでいて
Please don't let dawn come,
このままでいて
stay just like this.
その手を伸ばして 誰かに届くように
Reach out that hand, so it can touch someone...
本当に大切なものは 目に見えないみたいなんだ
It seems the things that are truly important are invisible to the eye.
そうさ僕は夜を歌うよ stellar stellar
Yes, I sing the night, stellar stellar,
ありのまま考えないで 今宵音楽はきっときっと止まらない
without overthinking, tonight the music surely won't stop!
そうだ僕がずっと泣きたかったのは
Yes, the reason I always wanted to cry...
会えないんじゃないじゃないさ
wasn't that I couldn't see you,
救いに行くヒーローだ
it was to be the hero coming to rescue you.
夢見がちな おとぎ話 おとぎ話
A dreamy fairy tale... a fairy tale...
そうさ僕は夜を歌うよ stellar stellar
Yes, I sing the night, stellar stellar,
ありったけの輝きで 今宵音楽はずっとずっと止まらない
with all my radiance, tonight the music will never, ever stop!
そうさ僕は愛を歌うよ stellar stellar
Yes, I sing love, stellar stellar,
世界、宇宙の真ん中で 今宵音楽はきっときっと止まらない
right in the center of the world, the universe, tonight the music surely won't stop!
そうだ僕がずっと泣きたかったのは
Yes, the reason I always wanted to cry...
待ってるシンデレラじゃないさ
wasn't to be a waiting Cinderella,
迎えに行く王子様だ
it was to be the prince coming to get you!
だって僕は星だから
Because I'm a star!
そうだ僕は星だった
Yes, I was a star.
stellar stellar
ミッドナイト・グランド・オーケストラで『夜を待つよ』、そして『Stellar Stellar』でした！
That was "Yoru wo Matsu yo" and "Stellar Stellar" by Midnight Grand Orchestra!
いかがでしたでしょうか！
How did you like it?
そしてタクノウエさん、今回の アレンジめっちゃいいですね！
And Taku Inoue-san, this arrangement is so good!
いや、めちゃくちゃよかった... アレンジャーの皆様ありがとうございます。
Man, it was awesome... Thank you so much to all the arrangers.
ありがとうございます！素晴らしい！
Thank you! Wonderful!
タクノウエさんもギター最高でしたよ！
Taku Inoue-san, your guitar was awesome too!
いや、緊張したわー！はい、ありがとうございました！
Man, I was so nervous! Thank you so much!
はい！
Yeah!
いつもね、聞いてたあの曲がこんな感じにアレンジされるんだっていうね
Realizing that the song we always listened to could be arranged like this...
いい意味での裏切りというか、すごいワクワクするアレンジになっているんじゃないかなと思います。
...is a pleasant surprise in a good way, and I think it turned into such an exciting arrangement.
そしてね、なんかここまでたくさんこの曲たちを歌ってきて
And, having sung all these songs up until now...
もう8年やってきたんだなっていうの、改めて実感しましたし
...it really made me realize once again that I've been doing this for 8 years now.
これからもね、星街すいせい
Going forward as well, Hoshimachi Suisei...
そして Midnight Grand Orchestra も末永くよろしくお願いします！
...and Midnight Grand Orchestra, we hope for your continued support for a long time!
ということで、特別ゲストの TAKU INOUE さんでした！
And with that, that was our special guest, TAKU INOUE!
ありがとうございました！TAKU INOUEでした！
Thank you very much! I was TAKU INOUE!
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you so much!
さて、楽しい時間はあっという間というところで
Now then, time flies when you're having fun, and...
次がいよいよ最後の曲になります。
...the next song will finally be the last one.
私自身、この曲が一番アコースティックになったらどうなるんだろうという感じで
For me, I was wondering what this song would sound like acoustic the most...
すごいね、バンドメンバーさんと合わせるのワクワクしておりました！
...so I was really excited to perform it together with the band members!
皆さんにも楽しんでもらえたら嬉しいです。
I hope you all enjoy it too.
それでは最後に聴いてください、『ソワレ』。
Now then, please listen to the final song: "Soirée".
あの黄昏も 折りたたむような静寂
A silence that seems to fold even that twilight away...
静寂
Quiet...
僕らの街じゃ暗がりは合図だ
In our town, darkness is the signal.
灯を消してはじめよう 幕よ開け
Turn off the lights and let's begin; open the curtain!
見上げ願いを あなたのように
Looking up, making a wish, just like you,
変わらず在っていたい
I want to remain unchanged.
きらめきのヴェールを
A sparkling veil,
目元に箔星描いて
drawing foil stars around my eyes.
瞬いたソワレ 今だ！
The twinkling soirée, now is the time!
寝息を立てる太陽の目を盗んで
Sneaking past the sleeping sun's gaze,
大脱走さ 逃げ出そうぜ
it's a grand escape, let's break away!
朝まだき空を跨ぐ 栞を挟んだら
Crossing the early morning sky, placing a bookmark...
行かなくちゃソワレ
I have to go, soirée,
夜が明けるまでさ
until the night breaks,
もう少しこのままで
just a little longer like this.
あの鐘の音は茜差したって止まらない
The sound of that bell won't stop even if the crimson light fades.
時間だ集まろう野望に喝采エールを
It's time, let's gather and cheer for our ambition!
未来の話を寂しそうに聞いてる君に
To you, who listen lonely to talk of the future,
誓うよ世界に魔法がなくたって
I swear, even if there's no magic in this world,
夢は続いていく
the dream will go on.
おやすみに代わるよう
As if replacing goodnight,
鳴りやまないメロディー届けて
delivering an unending melody.
見逃すなソワレ
Don't miss it, soirée,
僕ら目撃者だ
we are the witnesses!
蒼穹に手を伸ばした
Reaching out into the azure sky,
水平線がうたたねしたって
even if the horizon slumbers,
とめどなく日々を繋ぐ架け橋渡ったら
crossing the bridge that endlessly connects our days,
いつの日かソワレ
someday, soirée,
君に届くまでさ
until it reaches you,
何度でも呼び声を
no matter how many times, my calling voice...
消えない軌跡辿って
Following the unerasable tracks,
幾星霜の果てへ どこまでも
to the end of countless years, wherever it leads.
一晩じゃ語り尽くせない悲劇も
Even tragedies that can't be told in a single night,
一晩中語り明かせたら 喜劇になっていく
if talked through all night long, turn into comedies.
聴かせてよ
Let me hear it,
一筋の star tale
a single star tale.
瞬いたソワレ 今だ！
The twinkling soirée, now is the time!
寝息を立てる太陽の目を盗んで
Sneaking past the sleeping sun's gaze,
大脱走さ 逃げ出そうぜ
it's a grand escape, let's break away!
朝まだき空を跨ぐ 栞を挟んだら
Crossing the early morning sky, placing a bookmark...
約束だソワレ
It's a promise, soirée,
僕が眠るまでは
until I fall asleep,
何度でもまた明日
over and over again, see you tomorrow!
拝啓、ソワレ
Dear soirée,
君へ詠み継がれる 僕たちの
passed down to you, our...
物語
story.
ありがとうございました！
Thank you so much!
以上、星街すいせいでした！
That was Hoshimachi Suisei!
配信の方以上になりまーす！ お疲れ様でーす！
That's a wrap for the broadcast! Great work, everyone!
お疲れ様でした！
Great work, everyone!
Great job, everyone!
足元お気をつけください
Watch your step.
暗くなってます、お気をつけください
It's dark, please watch your step.
お疲れ様でした！
Great job, everyone!
Great job!
お疲れ様です！配信見てくれてますか？
Good evening! Were you watching the stream?
もちろんです。本当に、お疲れ様です。
Of course. Truly, great work out there.
この後、あの件発表してきます！
Right after this, I'm going to announce that matter!
胸を張って、自信を持って、お話ししてきてください。
Hold your head up high, be confident, and go speak to them.
はい！頑張ります！
Yes! I'll do my best!
改めて6周年記念生誕配信を見てくれて本当にありがとうございます。
Once again, thank you so much for watching my 6th anniversary birthday stream.
今日は私星街すいせいから皆さんに重大な発表があります。
Today, I, Hoshimachi Suisei, have a major announcement for all of you.
これまで長年、カバーさん、そしてホロライブプロダクションには本当にお世話になってきました。
Over the years, Cover and Hololive Production have truly taken great care of me.
長年の夢だった日本武道館など、たくさんの支えのおかげで夢をひとつひとつ叶えていくことができました。
Thanks to so much support, I was able to fulfill my dreams one by one, including Nippon Budokan.
感謝の気持ちを伝えられる機会がこれまであまりなかったのですが、
I haven't had many opportunities to express my gratitude until now,
谷郷さんをはじめ、ホロライブのタレントのみんな、スタッフの皆さん、関係してくださった皆さんに心からの感謝をしています。ありがとうございます。
but I am deeply grateful from the bottom of my heart to Mr. Tanigo, the Hololive talents, staff, and everyone involved.
その上で、東京ドームという次の目標に到達するためには、これからどうすればいいのかを考えてきました。
With that in mind, I've been thinking about what I need to do next to reach my next goal: Tokyo Dome.
昔に比べるとたくさんの方を見ていただけるようになりましたが、
Compared to the past, so many more people are watching me now,
それでもまだまだ越えなければいけない壁がたくさんあります。
but there are still many hurdles I need to overcome.
いろんなものと真剣に向き合い、そして考え抜いた結果、ひとつの大きな決断を下しました。
After facing various challenges seriously and giving it much thought, I have made one big decision.
びっくりさせてちゃうかもしれませんが、その発表を今日この場所でさせてください。
This might surprise you, but please allow me to make that announcement right here today.
個人事務所設立
[Establishing Personal Agency]
ということで、この度、星街すいせいは個人事務所を設立することになりました！
So, I, Hoshimachi Suisei, have established my own personal agency!
名称は「STUDIO STELLAR」！
Its name is "STUDIO STELLAR"!
今後の私個人の活動、日頃の配信、音楽活動、メディア出演、タイアップ、グッズ展開などなど、全てこのSTUDIO STELLARを拠点に行なっていくことになります！
All of my future individual activities—daily streams, music, media appearances, tie-ups, merchandise, and more—will be based out of STUDIO STELLAR!
と、こんな真面目なトーンで話すと...
Now, speaking in such a serious tone...
「えぇ〜！？すいちゃんホロライブ卒業！？」なんてね、思っちゃう人もいるんじゃないでしょうか！
"Ehh?! Suichan is graduating from Hololive?!" ...Some of you might be thinking that!
安心してください！ホロライブプロダクションとしての星街すいせいの活動もこれまで通り継続していきます！
Please rest assured! My activities as Hoshimachi Suisei of Hololive Production will continue as always!
ホロライブの大好きなみんなとの活動は引き続き思いっきり楽しみつつ、個人としてのさらなる高みを目指す場所がSTUDIO STELLARというすみ分けです。
While continuing to enjoy my activities with everyone in Hololive to the fullest, STUDIO STELLAR will be where I aim for even greater heights individually.
もっともっと大きなステージに立つための前向きで大きな決断なので、ぜひこれからも応援してもらえるとすごくすごく嬉しいです！
It's a positive and big step toward standing on even bigger stages, so I'd be super happy if you keep supporting me!
ちなみに、事務所の公式SNSもできましたので、今すぐフォローしてください！
By the way, the agency's official social media accounts are now live, so please go follow them right away!
IDは @ST_STELLAR_INFO です！
The handle is @ST_STELLAR_INFO!
この個人事務所設立をきっかけに、星街すいせいを構成するあらゆるクリエイティブをリニューアルしていきます。
With the establishment of this personal agency, we will be renewing all the creative elements that make up Hoshimachi Suisei.
どんどん発表していきますよ！準備はいいですかー？
I'll be announcing them one after another! Are you ready?
それでは1つ目！長年愛用してきた星街すいせいのロゴをリニューアルさせていただきました！
First up! We have renewed the Hoshimachi Suisei logo that I've been using for years!
こちら！
Here it is!
これまでのね、歴史とトーンはしっかり踏襲しつつ、今の時代に、そして今の私に一番フィットする形にデザインし直しました！
While honoring its history and tone, it has been redesigned into a form that best fits the current era and who I am today!
さらに！ずっと欲しかった私のシンボルマークも、なんと新しく誕生しましたよ！
Furthermore! A symbol mark for me, which I've wanted for so long, has also been newly created!
こちら！
Here it is!
いかがですか？可愛いね、王冠マークになっております！
How do you like it? It's a cute crown mark!
お次はアーティスト写真です！どうぞ！
Next up is my artist photo! Here you go!
はい！今回は夜の海で撮影してもらいました！これからの果てしない旅を感じさせるお気に入りの1枚になっております！
Yes! This time, it was shot by the sea at night! It's one of my favorite photos, giving a sense of the endless journey ahead!
まだまだありますよ！実はこれまでずっと無かったすいちゃんの公式ウェブサイトが、ついにオープンします！
There's still more! Suichan's official website, which didn't exist until now, is finally opening!
最新情報だったり、随時アップデートしていくので、毎日チェックしてくださいね！
Latest information and updates will be posted regularly, so please check it every day!
そしてそして、皆さんきっと待望であろう、公式ファンクラブも設立が決定しました！名前は「星詠み」！
And next, something you've all been eagerly waiting for: the official fan club is set to open! The name is "Hoshiyomi"!
...をファンクラブの名前にさせていただきました。
...and made that the name of our fan club.
これからももっとみんなの近くで、いろんなことを発信していきたいと思っております。
From now on, I want to share even more things with everyone from a closer distance.
ファンクラブ限定グッズが買えたり、チケットの先行申し込みができたり、
You can buy fan club exclusive merch, apply for early ticket presales,
会報誌、ラジオコンテンツなどなど、ファンクラブのために色々準備しているので、入会をお待ちしております！
access newsletters, radio content, and more. We're preparing lots of things for the fan club, so I look forward to your enrollment!
入会はこの配信終了後、21時からね。
Enrollment opens after this stream ends, at 9 PM!
ファンクラブができたということは、次に何が来るか、お分かりですよね？
And since a fan club has been launched, you know what comes next, right?
それでは、VTRどうぞー！
Without further ado, please watch this VTR!
HOSHIMACHI SUISEI ARENA TOUR 2026 "Once Upon a Stellar"
横浜 Kアリーナ横浜 / 神戸 GLION ARENA KOBE / 愛知 IGアリーナ / 福岡 マリンメッセ福岡A館
[Tour Venues: Yokohama, Kobe, Aichi, Fukuoka]
本日3月22日 21:00〜 ファンクラブ最速先行抽選受付開始
[Fan Club Presale Lottery Starts Today, March 22 at 21:00]
なんと！星街すいせい アリーナツアー、またしても開催決定！ありがとうございます！ドドン！
What a surprise! A Hoshimachi Suisei Arena Tour is officially happening once again! Thank you so much! Ta-da!
タイトルは「Once Upon a Stellar」！今回は4会場5公演でお届けします！
The title is "Once Upon a Stellar"! This time, we will bring you 5 performances across 4 venues!
9月8日、9月9日のKアリーナ横浜 2DAYSを皮切りに、
Starting with two days at K-Arena Yokohama on September 8th and 9th,
10月21日に GLION ARENA KOBE、
October 21st at GLION ARENA KOBE,
11月7日に名古屋 IGアリーナ、
November 7th at IG Arena Nagoya,
そして11月12日にマリンメッセ福岡 A館！
and November 12th at Marine Messe Fukuoka Hall A!
星街すいせい初となる4都市アリーナツアー、ぜひ遊びに来てください！
This will be Hoshimachi Suisei's very first 4-city arena tour, so please come see it!
お気づきの方もね、いると思うんですけれど、今回のライブキービジュアルも...
As some of you might have noticed, the key visual for this live tour is...
...カット！
...Cut!
お気づきの方もいるかもしれませんが、今回のライブキービジュアルは Mika Pikazo先生に描き下ろしていただきました！Mika先生本当にありがとうございます！
Some of you may have noticed, but the key visual for this tour was illustrated by Mika Pikazo-sensei! Thank you so much, Mika-sensei!
今回も本当に素敵なキービジュアルでね、ぜひたくさん見てください！
It's such a wonderful key visual again, so please check it out a lot!
チケットはなんと、本日の配信終了後から早速ファンクラブ先行申し込みがスタートします！絶対絶対チェックしてくださいね！
As for tickets, fan club presales will start right after today's stream ends! Be sure to check it out!
はい！次！実は、もう一つ騒がれていたあの大きなプロジェクトが動き出します。
Alright! Next! Actually, that big project everyone's been talking about is starting to move forward.
それでは、VTRをどうぞ！
Here is the VTR!
再起動 Restart
[Restart]
切り裂く静寂 全速前進
Cutting through silence, full speed forward,
生み出す引力で 光速のパッセージ
with generated gravity, a light-speed passage.
アレグロで今日も舞って
Dancing today in allegro as well.
消えない一拍を もっと紡いで
Spinning more of this everlasting beat,
打ち鳴らせ今日も万全で
sound it loud, fully prepared today as well.
しばらく眠っていたあのプロジェクト、Midnight Grand Orchestraも活動を改めて本格化していきます！
That project that was dormant for a while, Midnight Grand Orchestra, is resuming full-scale activities!
タイトルは「(2ND LIVE) PROJECT: ALLEGRO」。日程は2027年2月11日、場所は幕張メッセにてライブを行います！
The title is "(2ND LIVE) PROJECT: ALLEGRO". It will take place on February 11, 2027, at Makuhari Messe!
こちらも本日からファンクラブで先行申し込みができるので、ぜひぜひ遊びに来てください！
Fan club presales for this also begin today, so please do come along!
リリースだったり、タイアップなど、すでに色々決まっているものもありますので、星街すいせい、そしてMidnight Grand Orchestraのこれからを楽しみに待っていてくれると嬉しいです！
There are already various releases and tie-ins decided, so I hope you'll look forward to what's next for Hoshimachi Suisei and Midnight Grand Orchestra!
さて、すごい勢いで情報を出していきましたが、皆さんついて来れておりますでしょうか？
Well, I've dumped a lot of information at a crazy pace, but were you all able to keep up?
今日発表したことは全部ね、次の大きな目標に向けて、私が本当に頑張りたいと思って、たくさん悩んだ末に決断をしたことです。
Everything announced today consists of decisions I made after much agonizing, all aimed at working really hard toward my next major goal.
環境は少し変わるかもしれないんですが、星街すいせいはもちろんこれからもずっと私らしくあり続けます。
My environment may change a bit, but Hoshimachi Suisei will naturally continue being true to myself forever.
これからもどうか一緒に夢を追いかけてくれると嬉しいです。よろしくお願いします！
I'd be so happy if you keep chasing dreams together with me. Thank you for your support!
さて、それでは最後に、3つ...まだ3つもある！3つだけお知らせをして今日の配信を終わりたいと思います。
Now then, lastly, 3 more... there are still 3 more! I'll make just 3 quick announcements and wrap up today's stream.
まず1つ目！
First, the first announcement!
今日は皆さん、お忘れじゃないですよね？
Everyone, you haven't forgotten what day today is, right?
私の誕生日でもあるということで
Since it's also my birthday,
生誕グッズはもちろんご用意しております！
we naturally have birthday merchandise prepared for you!
Tシャツ、ステッカーセット、アクスタ、全部入りボックスに加えて、ファンクラブ限定のTシャツなどなど、どれもデザインにこだわりましたので、ぜひ手に入れてください！
T-shirts, sticker sets, acrylic stands, a full set box, and a fan club exclusive T-shirt—we put so much care into every design, so please check them out!
2つ目！
Second!
星街すいせいライブツアー2024「Spectra of Nova」
Hoshimachi Suisei Live Tour 2024 "Spectra of Nova"
星街すいせい日本武道館ライブ「Supernova」
and Hoshimachi Suisei Nippon Budokan Live "Supernova"—
この2つのBlu-rayの通常盤が予約受付開始します！
pre-orders for both standard edition Blu-rays are now open!
予約は本日22時からスタートです！
Pre-orders start tonight at 10:00 PM!
今回のBlu-rayは以前のようなセット販売はなく、ツアー、武道館それぞれの個別での販売のみになります。
Unlike previous releases, these Blu-rays won't be sold as a bundle, but individually for the tour and Budokan.
そしてツアーのBlu-rayは、埼玉公演のみの映像化となっています。
Also, the tour Blu-ray features footage strictly from the Saitama concert.
ただし！特典映像として、他のツアー公演の楽曲も一部収録されております！
However, select songs from other tour stops are included as bonus footage!
ゲストパートとか...
Like guest performances...
何が収録されているかは、ぜひBlu-rayでチェックしてみてください！
Be sure to check out the Blu-ray to see what made the cut!
なお、今回は去年販売したBlu-rayとは仕様が少し異なり、ツアーBlu-rayの特典映像以外の特典は付属していませんので、ご注意ください。
Note that specs differ slightly from last year's release; no bonuses other than the bonus video content are included with the tour Blu-ray.
ただ！その分ね、お買い求めやすい価格になっておりますので、詳しくは特設サイトや公式X、公式Twitterをチェックしてください！
However, that makes them more affordable, so check the special site or official X (Twitter) for details!
そして、3つ目！
And third!
皆さん、お待たせしました！
Everyone, thank you for waiting!
毎年恒例ですが、新曲が出ます！
As per our annual tradition, a new song is coming out!
タイトルは『プリマドンナ』！
The title is "Primadonna"!
この配信が終わった後、21時半からミュージックビデオのプレミア公開が始まります！
Right after this stream, the music video premiere will start at 9:30 PM!
これからの星街すいせいの名刺代わりになるような、すごくテンションが上がる曲に仕上がっております！
It's an incredibly high-energy song that will serve as Hoshimachi Suisei's calling card moving forward!
概要欄に貼っているURLから飛べるので、ぜひ楽しみにしていてください！
You can open it via the link in the description, so please look forward to it!
絶対に待機していてください！
Make sure to wait on the premiere page!
ということで、以上で星街すいせい8周年記念生誕配信を終わります！
And with that, this concludes the Hoshimachi Suisei 8th Anniversary Birthday Stream!
今日は本当にありがとうございました！
Thank you all so much for today!
新しいSTUDIO STELLARの星街すいせいも、どうかどうかよろしくお願いいたします！
Please continue to support Hoshimachi Suisei at the new STUDIO STELLAR!
それでは、またねー！
Until next time, see you later!
最後までみてくれてありがとう☆ これからも私は私らしく、みんなと共にあります。新しい挑戦を続けて、まだ見ぬ世界を見に行こう！ 星街すいせい
[On-Screen Note: Thank you for watching until the end ☆ I will stay true to myself and continue to stand with you all. Let's keep taking on new challenges and explore unseen worlds together! — Hoshimachi Suisei]
最後までみてくれてありがとう☆彡
Thank you for watching until the end!
これからも私は私らしく、みんなと共にあります。
I'll continue to be true to myself and stay by everyone's side.
新しい挑戦を続けて、まだ見ぬ世界を見に行こう！
Let's keep taking on new challenges and explore unseen worlds!